■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
《南方公园》第18季  第3集
"娘炮"
I'm going down to south park
gonna have myself a time
Friendly faces everywhere
humble folks without temptation
Going down to south park
gonna leave my woes behind
Ample parking day or night
people shouting howdy neighbor
Heading on out to south park
gonna see if I can't unwind
I like girls with big vaginas
I like girls with big fat titties
Come on down to south park
and meet some friends of mine.
翻译：西西    foxap    八哥    半半    胡好时    CS小明漫画家
校对：吃货丁小七    时间轴：marktaotao    灵媒
又是一个等着破校车
Another morning, waiting for the rundown school bus
后期：鱼骨头      总监：吃货丁小七
把我带去那个破学校的早晨
to take me to the rundown school.
但今天我终于有足够的勇气
But today is the day I finally have the guts to do
去做一件我很久前就该做的事情
what I should have done a long time ago.
没人知道我在口袋里放了什么
Nobody notices what I have in my front pocket.
这是给所有人的惊喜
A little surprise for them all.
虽然已经做好准备  但我仍然在想
I prepared for this, but still I wonder,
我到底有没有勇气完成这件事情呢
will I have the guts to go through with it?
我他妈肯定行
Yeah, damn right I will.
你还好吗  卡特曼
Are you okay, Cartman?
我很好  你怎么样  凯尔
Yeah, I'm good! How are you, Kyle?
他们都要付出代价
They're all gonna pay.
日复一日  他们压迫着我
Every day, they've pushed me and pushed me,
如果今天还是老样子
and if it happens again today,
这将是最后一次
it's going to be the last time.
我们会在午休时得到答案
We'll find out today at recess, won't we?
没错  午休时分见分晓
Oh, yes, we'll find out today at recess.
南方公园小学
男厕所  女厕所
记得洗手
埃里克  他们让我回来了
Hey, Eric! I'm not suspended no more.
挺好
Good for you.
我觉得里面有人了
I think someone is in it.
他妈的  不
No, god damn it, no!
谁在里面拉屎
Who's taking the shit?!
有人了
Occupied!
午休时间一号蹲位都是我的  克雷格
I called dibs on stall one for all recess, Craig!
你不能霸占马桶
You can't call dibs on a toilet.
狗娘养的  不
Son of a bitch. Oh, no.
不  我不能再过一个上不成厕所的午休了
No, no, no. I cannot go another lunch break without my toilet time!
那就别连吃14个爱家华夫饼  死胖子
Then don't eat 14 Eggo waffles for lunch, fatass!
好了  够了
All right, that does it!
老子受够了
I'm sick of this shit and I'm not taking it any longer!
是你们逼我的
You all pushed me to this!
你这是要做什么
What the hell do you think you are doing?
我要去上厕所
I'm going to the potty.
这是女生的卫生间
This is the girl's bathroom!
温蒂  我得告诉你件事
All right, I need to tell you something, Wendy.
我是变性淫
I'm transginger.
你看到这个蝴蝶结了吗
Did you notice the bow?
我不喜欢我先天的性别
I'm not comfortable with the sex I was assigned at birth,
我在享受我的权利  选择我喜欢的性别
so I'm exercising my right to identify with the gender of my choice.
现在滚一边去  我要拉屎了
Now get out of my way. I have to take a shit.
你赶紧出去
Get out of here!
别再逼我了  温蒂
Don't give me more issues than I already have, Wendy.
这里真棒
Oh, wow. This is nice in here.
女生的卫生间比男生的干净太多了
The girls' bathroom is a lot cleaner than the boys.
搞什么啊
What the hell is that?
卡特曼在用我们的卫生间
Cartman is using our bathroom!
这太棒了  我早就该来女生的卫生间了
Dude, this is awesome! I should have used the girls'  bathroom a long time ago!
我要去告发你
I'm gonna tell on you!
随便你  红毛妞
It's okay, Red.
我可以在这里拉屎
I can take a shit here.
现在我也是脑残女生的一员了
I'm a dumb chick too.
我想知道  你凭什么觉得
I want to know just what makes you think it's okay
你可以进到女生的卫生间去
to go inside the girls'  bathroom!
因为我是变性淫
Because I'm transginger.
我查过了  这说明我可以用女生的马桶
I looked it up. That means I can use the girls' shitter.
奶牛向前冲
埃里克  你不是变性人
You are not transgender, Eric.
你甚至不知道那是什么意思
You don't even know what that means.
谁说的  这说明我的一生饱受折磨和困惑
Yeah-huh, it means I live a life of torture
因为社会把我当成男生
and confusion because society sees me as a boy
但我实际上是女生
but I'm really a girl.
好吧  既然你觉得自己是个女生
All right, well, if you identify yourself as a girl,
那你应该喜欢男生
you must find yourself attracted to boys.
对吗
Is that right?
这是不对的
That's actually not true.
我是变性淫的事情
I can be transginger without it having anything to do
和我喜欢哪个性别的人没有关系
with the ginger I'm attracted to.
法律是这么规定的
Check this state by laws.
好吧  埃里克  听我说
All right, listen, Eric.
-叫我艾丽卡  -听我说  埃里克
- Erika. - Listen, Eric.
[美国法律规定  变性人有权在变性后采用新名字  他人应当用新名字来称呼他/她]
你要明白为什么
You must know why
我们不能让你去女生的卫生间
we can't have you in the girls' bathroom.
我只知道我是变性淫
All I know is I'm transginger
你不能让我跟正常淫一起上厕所
and you can't make me go to the bathroom with the cisgingers.
和谁
With the what?
原性人
Cisgender.
这是从政治角度对非变性人的正确称呼
It's the politically correct name for people who aren't transgender.
若你认同出生时的性别  你就是原性人
If you identify with the sex you're born with, then you are cis.
但是原性人就是正常人啊
But then cisgender is just normal.
使用"正常人"就是对不属于这类的人
Saying "normal" is extremely offensive to people
极大的冒犯
who aren't in that group.
相信我  你们不会想碰这个烫手山芋的
Trust me. You don't want this hot potato.
让他用他的女厕所吧
Just let him use the girls' room.
但这并非是某个伤心  迷茫的孩子
But this isn't a hurting, confused child we're talking about.
这可是埃里克・卡特曼
This is Eric Cartman.
别人可不知道这一点
Nobody else is gonna know that.
你最好还是遂了他的心意
You better just give him what he wants.
埃里克・卡特曼真在厕所上把我们将死了
So Eric Cartman just has us in some kind of bathroom checkmate?
实际上
Actually...
这更像是个同花顺
it's more like a royal flush.
杰拉德・布洛夫斯基吗
Gerald Broflovski?
什么事
Yes?
我叫布兰登・卡莱尔
Brandon Carlile,
《斯宾》杂志的记者
reporter, Spin magazine.
《斯宾》  美国著名音乐杂志
我希望您能帮我弄清某件事情
I was hoping you could help me make sense of something.
我了解到上周日  在您的后院
I understand that you had a very large party in your backyard
有一场盛大的派对是吧
last... last Sunday was it?
没错  我儿子和他的小伙伴们
That's right. My son and his friends threw a party
为一位有糖尿病的男孩办了场派对
for a kid with diabetes.
我还了解到著名的流行歌星洛儿
I also understand that the very famous pop artist Lorde
曾在派对上演唱
was the entertainment at that party.
是的  没错  孩子们乐坏了
Oh, yeah, yeah, the kids were pretty excited.
我只是有点好奇
Well, it--it's just a little curious, you know?
为什么一个排名前20的歌星会在
Why a hugely popular, top-20 artist would play such a--
无意冒犯  如此低档的地方演唱呢
well, no offense--but such a humble venue?
抱歉  我不太明白你的
Sorry. I don't think I get your--
您要知道
You understand,
我们在《斯宾》经常应对假新闻
we deal with a lot of fake stories at Spin.
我只是好奇孩子们如何能请到洛儿这种人
We're just wondering how the boys got someone like Lorde to play.
据我所知  她好像是
From what I understand, she's the niece
镇上谁的同事的侄女
of someone's co-worker here in town or something.
不知道是谁吗
You wouldn't know who?
不知道  这点很重要吗
No. Does it really matter?
洛儿是一个非常有天赋并且接地气的女孩
Lorde is an incredibly talented and down-to-earth young lady.
如果她得为别人的玩笑买单就太过分了
It would be a shame if someone was...having fun at her expense.
兰迪  这些是谁的
Randy, whose are these?
不知道啊  怎么了
I don't know. Why?
怎么了
Why?
因为是在你的牛仔裤里发现的渔网黑丝
Because there's fishnet stockings inside your jeans?
我的牛仔裤里
In my jeans?
兰迪  你有什么要跟我坦白的吗
Randy, do you have something to tell me?
好吧  我说
Yeah. I do.
快点  你都在里面待了20分钟了
Come on! You've been in there for 20 minutes.
是的  马上就要上课了
Yeah! Recess is almost over!
还有两个坑呢女孩们  去上啊
There's two more stalls in here, gals. Go ahead.
你在这里怎么上
Not while you're in here.
天呐
Oh, my god.
你们太原性人了  抱歉我跟你们不一样
You guys are so cisgender. Sorry I'm different,
你们还是可以跪舔我的豆豆和蛋蛋的
but you can suck my clit and my balls.
埃里克  有些人是真在
Eric, there are people actually struggling
为自己的性别苦恼  可你却是在...
with their gender identity, and all you're doing is...
好吧  好吧  伙计们
Okay, okay, okay, you guys.
知道吗  知道吗
You know what? You know what?
就是这个
That's what.
跪舔我的豆豆和蛋蛋吧
Suck my clit and my balls.
艾丽卡  我们找到解决问题的办法了
Erica, I believe we have a solution to this little problem.
维多利亚校长  我可没问题
I don't have a problem, Principal Victoria.
有问题的是那些原性人
The cisgenders have the problem.
如果你同意的话  艾丽卡
If it is agreeable to you, Erica...
我们打算清出清洁工的储物间
we are going to clear out the janitor's closet
然后将其改造为
and remodel it...
你专人使用的厕所
into a private bathroom just for you!
您说什么
Excuse me?
您是说我的私人订制厕所吗
Are you talking about my own special, executive bathroom?
你看这样可以吗
Would that be agreeable to you?
-我的天呐  -这不公平
- Oh, my god! - That isn't fair!
温蒂  还是算了吧
Wendy, just go with it.
一边羡慕去吧  温蒂  原性人小婊砸
Yeah, just go with it, Wendy. Cisginger bitch.
当然了  被迫使用独享的厕所
Of course, being forced into my own isolated bathroom
可能会在某种程度上对我造成创伤
will probably be somewhat traumatic for me.
我可能还需要对里面的布置做更多的考量
I might have to approve certain aspects of this solitary location.
清洁工储物间
我想要在这弄个庭园水景
Yeah, so, I'm thinking a water feature here--you know,
潺潺的流水声颇有禅意
get the sound of running water and kind of zen it out.
为嘛不把庭园水景放这边呢
Uh-huh, well, why don't you put the water feature on this side.
放那边吗
Oh, on that side?
因为你这边已经有空调啦
You know, because you've already got A/C over here
这样的话这边就能空出来
and that leaves this open
在墙上挂一大幅精美的艺术作品了
for some nice big piece of art on this wall.
这点子我喜欢  听上去也不错
Oh, I like that. That sounds really nice too.
[此处用了《绝命毒师》背景音乐  暗示兰迪的双重生活]
听着
Yeah, listen.
我不知道我还能坚持多久
I don't know if I can keep doing this.
我老婆已经开始有所怀疑了
My wife is starting to suspect something.
我不得不告诉她我喜欢穿渔网黑丝的感觉
I had to tell her I just like the way fishnets feel!
我知道你的妻子对你来说很重要  兰迪
I know your wife means a lot to you, Randy,
可你不能对我们置之不理啊
but you can't leave us hanging.
你的创意最纯粹了  对我们来说价值连城
You've got the purest shit out there and it's worth a lot to us.
要是我想不出来了你们还能有好作品吗
You think you're gonna get a good product when I can't even think?
你这话都说过多少遍了
How many times have you said,
"我想我黔驴技穷了"  可结果都挺好的
"I think I've lost it," And everything turned out to be OK.
每次都是吗
Every time?
每次都是  加油吧
Every time. Come on.
回去干活吧  要是你又恐慌了再打给我
Get back to work and see. If you get panicked again, call me.
好吧
Yeah.
我会的
Yeah, I will. Yeah.
快试试转得快车轴吧
你想见我吗
You wanted to see me?
坐下 荣恩
Sit down, Ron.
你对我们的那位艺术家洛儿了解多少
What do you know about one of our artists, Lorde?
来自新西兰的17岁女生
17-year-old girl from New Zealand.
很棒的创作歌手  为人谦虚
Great song writer, humble.
错
Wrong.
她是个45岁的男人  住在科罗拉多
She's a 45-year-old man living in Colorado.
啥
What?
他写歌  发给我们试听  我们瞎搞搞
He writes the songs, sends us the demos, we futz them,
把他包装成一个忧郁早熟的17岁少女
sell him as a brooding 17-year-old girl way ahead of her time.
没人听得出差别
And nobody knows the difference.
我擦咧
Huh. Holy shit.
他能写好歌  大卖的歌
He makes good stuff. Stuff that sells.
可他靠不住  我想让你监视他
But he's getting itchy feet. I want you to keep an eye on him.
要是发现有人看起来像要
And if anyone around him seems like
识破事情的真相
they're close to finding out the truth, well...
你知道该怎么做
You know what to do.
*洛儿  洛儿  洛儿  我是洛儿*
*Lorde Lorde Lorde Lorde Lorde Lorde, I am Lorde*
*我是洛  我是洛儿  我是洛儿*
*I am Lo... I am Lorde I am Lorde*
兰迪
Randy?
我以为你去买菜了
Ah! I thought you were at the grocery store.
我是去了  你能来帮我搬东西吗
I was. Can you help me unload the car?
帮我搬东西
"Help me unload the car."
*帮我搬东西  搬东西  呀呀呀*
*Help me unload... unload the car, yeah yeah yeah*
*搬  搬  呀呀呀*
*Unload un--unload... yeah yeah yeah*
-兰迪  -抱歉  来了
- Randy? - Sorry, sorry, yeah. Coming.
其他
那是啥
What is that?
那是卡特曼的新变性洗手间
That's Cartman's new transgender bathroom.
卡特曼现在变女生了吗
Cartman's a girl now?
他不是女的
He's not a woman.
[化用歌手普林斯・罗杰斯・内尔森的《I Would Die 4 U》歌词
普林斯曾自创一个雌雄同体符号作为自己的名字]
也不是男的  他是你不了解的物种
He's not a man. He is something that you'll never understand.
可他会为了我去死
But he would die for me.
好了吗  都弄好了吗
Is it done? It's all ready?
好啦  好啦  大家让让  请让开
All right, all right, move aside everybody, move aside, please.
我要去洗手间
I gotta go!
真是棒呆了
Oh, oh, this is gonna be so awesome.
锁上  私人空间
Lock. Privacy.
一定很爽
Oh, this is gonna feel so good.
完美
Perfect.
有你受的
Yeah, you're gonna take it.
就剩你了  马桶  叫破喉咙也没人能听见
You're all alone now, toilet. Nobody can hear you scream.
给我张大一点  接受你应有的惩罚
Yeah, you're gonna open wide. You're gonna take your punishment!
就是这样  受死吧
That's right! Get ready!
天呐  爽歪歪  各位  有家的感觉
Oh, my God! This is so awesome, you guys. It's just like at home.
斯基特的酒吧及鸡尾酒
皮特・纳尔逊
Peter Nelson?
有何贵干
Yes?
我是布兰登・卡利  《斯宾》杂志记者
Brandon Carlile, reporter, Spin Magazine.
我知道你在美国地质调查局工作
I understand you work at the... U.S. Geological Survey.
是的
Yeah. That's right.
我还知道你是那个才华横溢的作曲家
I also understand that you're the uncle of the amazing
洛儿的叔叔
and talented songwriter Lorde?
好吧  听着  我可不是她的叔叔
All right, look. I'm not her uncle.
我只是和她在一起上班  好吧
I just work with her, OK?
和她一起工作  怎样
Work with her? How?
我喜欢洛儿  她人非常好也非常有才华
I like Lorde. She's really nice and really talented.
但是她过着双重生活
But she lives double life.
什么双重生活
How's that?
洛儿不仅是歌手  还是个很有天赋的科学家
Lorde isn't just a singer. She's also a very talented scientist
她是研究河流地貌学的专家
who specializes in fluvial geomorphology.
她  什么
She? What?
她某天突然出现在办公室
She just showed up one day at the office,
开始代替一位兼职人员做他的工作
started filling in for a guy who started working part-time.
她是一位很棒的地质学家
She's a good geologist.
她的音乐事业爆红以后我们还以为她不会来了
When her music career took off, we thought she'd be gone,
但是她还是出现了  一般吃过午饭来
but She still shows up, usually right after lunch.
荣誉墙
嗨  卡特曼
Hey, Cartman.
听说你是个变性人
Heard you're a transgender.
是啊  那你知道希拉里说了什么吗
Yup! You know what Hillary says.
你可以舔我的克林顿蛋蛋
You can suck my Clinton balls!
不  我根本不可能做完  我发誓
No, I'm not even gonna get it done, I swear.
不管怎么样他作业布置太多了  我
He gives us too much homework anyways, I--
大家好
Hey guys
温蒂
Wendy?
感觉如何
How's it hanging?
等等  那是
W-w-wait, is that--
天啦撸
Holy molly!
喂  你他妈干什么啊
Hey! What the fuck, dude?
不介意嘛你  这正用着呐
Do you mind? This is occupied!
没关系  我会等
It's cool. I'll wait.
哥们儿  这他妈可是我的厕所
Dude, this is my fucking bathroom!
我要求她停止  还要告她性骚扰
I want her suspended and I want charges brought up for sexual harassment.
抱歉艾丽卡  可今早我已经和温兜谈过了
I'm sorry, Erica, but I spoke with Wendyl this morning
而且她感到不自在
and she's not comfortable--
温兜  操他妈的温兜
"Wendyl"? fucking "Wendyl"?
成熟点  温蒂
Grow up, Wendy.
你要学会和人分享  埃里克
You'll just have to share, Eric.
为什么你就不能理解这件事呢
Why can't you understand that?
因为我不想被一个小妞看着便便
because I don't want a chick watching me go poo!
我还以为你也是小妞
I thought you were a chick.
不  我以为自己是个小妞但我还是男的
No, I identify as a chick but I'm still a boy.
你不能让我跟一个以为自己是男的的小妞
You can't make me share a bathroom with a girl
共用一个厕所
that identifies herself as a fucking dude!
那是我的瀑布  还有我的圣诞彩灯
That is my waterfall and those are my Christmas lights!
伙计  把你家的狗栓牢一点
Dude, you need to put a tight leash on your dog.
什么
What?
你知道你女朋友在到处说你是同性恋吗
Do you know your girlfriend's going around telling everyone that you're gay?
还有
Oh, yeah!
她让整个学校的人都相信  她只喜欢女的
She's got the whole school believing that she's attracted to girls,
可她正和你在约会呢  那你算个毛线啊斯坦
but she's dating you! So what does that make you, Stan?
女孩子
A girl!
斯坦是个女孩子  看好你的狗  斯坦
Stan's a girl! You better curb your dog, Stan!
在大家嘲笑你之前  看住你的狗
You better curb your dog before people start ripping on you!
谢莉  手机玩够久了
Shelley, that's enough time on your phone.
不要烦我老爸  别一直唠叨个不停
Leave me alone, dad! Stop nagging me all the time!
我们说好一起减少玩手机的时间的
You know we're all cutting down on phone time.
别老是限制我   你根本就不懂我
Don't limit me! You don't even understand me!
洛儿
是  我一点都不懂你
Yeah, I don't understand you at all.
非常不懂你
Lot you know.
老爸  我得跟你谈谈
Oh, hey, dad. I need to talk to you.
是吗  关于什么
Oh, really? About--about what?
老爸  这世上有人能够内心和外表
Dad, is it possible for someone to be one way on the outside
完全是两个不同的人吗
but totally different on the inside?
我的意思是  有人可以自以为是一种性别
I mean, can someone identify as one sex
实际上是另一种性别而且跟性别无关吗
but be something else but still have it be nothing about sex.
是的  是的  斯坦
Yes. Yes, Stan.
我就是洛儿
I am Lorde.
什么
What?
开始的时候原因很简单
It started off so simple.
我的同事  汉森
There's a guy at work-- Hansen.
他上厕所总是溅得到处都是
He would use the bathroom and just blow the thing up, you know?
不仅如此  他还老是霸占着厕所
Not only that but he was in there all the time.
最终我忍无可忍  就假扮成了女人
I finally got fed up. I pretended to be a woman.
我给自己取名叫洛儿
I called myself Lorde.
你有去过女厕所吗  斯坦
Have you ever been in a woman's Bathroom, Stan?
那里超干净  而且每个人都有足够的位置
It's all clean and there's enough stalls for everyone.
感觉超自在
It was so freeing.
我开始在厕所里唱歌
I started singing while I was in there and then I
然后开始写歌
started writting things down.
但你说你同事是洛儿的叔叔啊
But you said you knew a guy at work who's Lorde's uncle.
是  那是我的伪装
Yeah, that's my cover.
给《饥饿游戏》写主题曲的那小妞
The chick that wrote the theme song to the new Hunger Games movie
是你啊
is you?
是的  唱片公司把歌全改了
Yeah, the record company messed it all up.
它本来应该是
It was supposed to go...
*饥饿游戏  呀呀呀  呀呀呀  饥饿游戏*
*Hunger games ya ya ya ya ya ya hunger games*
但他们就是随便篡改我的歌
But they just do what they want with my songs.
等等  洛儿的声音是个女孩啊
Wait, Lorde sounds like a girl.
魔音软件  你想看看我是怎么做的吗
Autotune. You want to see how I do it?
我最棒的歌都是在公司厕所里写出来的
I come up with all my best stuff in the bathroom at work.
然后把我用手机录的歌导入这个软件
I use this program to import the recordings I make on my phone.
*呀  呀  周三的早晨真开心*
*Yeah yeah feelin' good on a Wednesday*
*思想的火花给我活下去的希望*
*Sparklin' thoughts give me the hope to go on*
*我现在需要一个港湾*
*What I need now is a little bit shelter...*
爸  洛儿的歌其实很好听
Dad, Lorde's music is actually really good.
谢谢
Thanks.
但当我加入鼓点后  效果更好
But it gets even better when I add the drum loops.
*呀  呀  周三的早晨真开心*
*Yeah yeah feelin' good on a Wednesday*
然后我可以用电脑量化所有细节
Then with the computer, I can actually quantize everything.
来点辅助乐器
Some backup instruments.
最后使用魔音功能
And then finally I use the autotune.
*思想的火花给我活下去的希望*
*Sparklin' thoughts give me the hope to go on*
*给我希望  给我给我活下去的希望*
*giving me the hope giving giving me the hope to go on*
*我现在需要一个港湾*
*What I need now is a little bit shelter...*
斯坦
Stan?
南方公园小学
你还好么  斯坦
Hey, everything okay, Stan?
我不知道何去何从
I don't know where I belong.
忍着吧  学学我
Just hold it. That's what I do now.
你妹  你想干嘛
Hey! What the fuck, dude?
你大爷啊
God fucking damn it!
干脆让所有人都用变性淫厕所好了
Why don't we just have everyone use the transginger bathroom?
斯坦利  你为什么不用男生洗手间
Stanley, do you have a reason for not using the boys' bathroom?
我只是  我的两个亲友有性别认知的问题
I just--two people close to me are having gender identity issues
而我很困扰
and I'm confused.
他是原性人  他原到都要穿护裆睡觉
He's cisginger! He's so cis he wears a jockstrap to bed at night!
美国地质勘测院  科罗拉多分局
您找我么  老大
You wanted to see me, boss?
是的  请坐  洛儿
Yes, please have a seat, Lorde.
你好啊  卡罗
Hi, Caro.
好啊  洛儿
Lorde.
洛儿  我们都超爱你的音乐
Lorde, we're all big fans of your music
你在成名后继续留在这里工作
and we think the world of you for staying and working here
对我们而言也很重要
even after your music career took off.
我的音乐事业和流水地貌的研究是不可分割的
Well, my music and fluvial geomorphology are intertwined.
真棒
Amazing, yeah.
洛儿  有些时候
Uh, Lorde, for some time now,
公司里的女同事迫切希望
the females at this office have been pressuring me to...
我能给你一个单独的卫生间
find your own space to go to the bathroom.
大家都很爱你
Everyone loves you,
然而我们认为
but we thought it would be great
如果你能用你的专属卫生间就太好了
if you had your very own executive bathroom.
我很喜欢女洗手间啊
I like the women's bathroom.
那里很有安全感
I feel safe there.
那个洗手间对我的性别认知和音乐都很重要
Being able to use that bathroom is critical to my identity, to my music!
我女儿们都是你的狂热粉  洛儿
My girls are big fans of your music, Lorde,
但是女同事们都不太乐意跟你这样的共用厕所
but the women here aren't comfortable sharing a bathroom with--
哪样的
With what?
您正在收看"E娱乐播报"
You are watching E! Entertainment news.
爱得痛  陷得深
That's how low you've sunk.
若干天过去了
It's been several days and
然而还是不见流行歌手洛儿的踪迹
still there's no sign of the pop singer, Lorde.
寻找洛儿
她消失前表示有严重抑郁  最后一条微博称
The singer went dark on twitter after claiming severe depression and stating...
"我意识到自己让人们感到不舒服
I realize now that I make people uncomfortable.
我会离开并做回原来的自己"
I need to give this up and go back to just being the old me.
寻找洛儿
《斯宾》周刊声称知道她退出娱乐圈的原因
Spin magazine is claiming they know the reason for the sudden exit
并将在下周公布关于该艺人的完整内幕
and will be releasing a tell-all article about the troubled artist next week.
南方公园小学
各位  他来了
Oh, here he comes, everyone.
原性淫来了
It's the cisginger.
你以为你可以骚扰变性淫并夺取他们的厕所吗
Think you can harass transgingers and use their bathroom?
那你为什么要骚扰艾丽卡  斯坦
Yeah, what's the big idea harassing Erica, Stan?
这所学校里  你是否变性并不要紧
At this school, it doesn't matter if you're trans or you're cis.
-对不对伙计们  -没错
- Right? Guys? - Yeah!
我们不能接受的是肚量狭窄的原性人
What we have a problem with are cisgingers who are intolerant!
知道我们称他们什么吗
You know what we call those?
-娘炮  -没错
- Cissies - Yeah!
斯坦是个又老又胖的娘炮
Stan is a big old fat cissy!
算了  别围着他了  伙计们
Oh, come on, lay off him guys,
怎么  你也是娘炮不成
Oh, what, are you a cissy?
不不  只有他是
No, no, just he is.
你要一个人喝一天啤酒吗
You just gonna drink beer alone all day?
没事的  不含谷蛋白
It's okay. It's gluten-free.
好吧
All right.
知道为什么年轻人那么喜欢洛儿吗
Do you know why young people like Lorde so much?
因为她与众不同
It's because she's something different.
孩子被流行音乐家喷了一脸黄暴
Kids have had pop music artists flash tits and crotch in their face
其实大多数聪明孩子觉得那些很恶心
and most kids are actually smart enough to be sick of it.
洛儿表达了我们都有的某些特质
Lorde represents something in all of us
一种真实的声音
a truth that wants to be heard.
如果我能跟洛儿聊一聊  知道我会说什么吗
If I could talk to Lorde right now, you know what I'd tell her?
我会告诉她  别被人们所改变
I'd tell her not to let people change who she is.
我会说  如果人们取笑她
I'd tell her that if people are making fun of her,
那可能是因为他们已经忘了如何做人
it's probably because they've lost touch with being human.
我会要她继续她的事业
I'd tell her to keep on doing what she does.
因为当人们被禁止表达真实的自己时
Because when someone's not allowed to express who they are inside,
我们都会迷失
then we all lose.
这就是  我要对洛儿说的
That's... what I'd say to Lorde.
*某个周三  感觉良好*
*Feelin' good on a Wednesday*
*你所看到  我的形容*
*The image of me that you see*
*如毁坏扭曲破败的枯骨*
*Is distorted twisted broken fractured*
*在那与世隔绝的远海*
*Isolated miles out to sea*
*我不要与世隔绝*
*I don't want a separate place*
*我要安全感  不要被抛诸脑后*
*I need to feel safe not thrown away away away away*
*我要推倒高墙*
*And I will push push to tear down the walls*
*我要推倒你关押我的牢笼*
*Push push of this box you put me in*
*推吧推吧  因为你不懂*
*Push push because you don't understand*
*推啊  火热地推吧*
*push ow hot push ow ow hot ya ya ya*
*我要推倒*
*And I will push*
*找到适合我的标签*
*To find a label that fits me*
*某个周三  当墙被推倒时*
*I'm feelin' good on a Wednesday*
*我感觉良好  请给我提示*
*When the walls are falling down. Help me on the note card*
*所以我要推开*
*And so I push*
*那扇紧闭的门*
*To close the door*
*你围住我那间屋子的门*
*Of the stall you've made for me*
*为了拒我于千里之外*
*To keep me away*
*现在我们一起推*
*And now we push*
*只为相聚  因为我是洛儿*
*Push to stand together because I am Lorde*
洛儿是个45岁的男地理学家
*我是洛儿*
*Ya ya ya ya ya ya I am Lorde*
*我是洛儿  我是洛儿*
*I am Lorde ya ya ya ya ya ya I am Lorde*
删除
*我是洛儿  我是洛儿*
*I am Lorde ya ya ya ya ya ya I am Lorde*
南方公园小学
我在这里骄傲地宣布  经学生投票决定
And so it is with great pride that I can announce the student body
我们要移除变性人卫生间门上的标志
has elected to get rid of the transgender bathroom.
并给予所有学生这项权利
And give any fellow student the right
可以使用你们最愿意使用的卫生间
to use the bathroom they feel most comfortable in.
要是所有人都能用  我才不要再去女厕所呢
I don't want to use the girls' bathroom if anyone can use it!
肯定会人满为患了
It's gonna be all crowded.
如果有谁不愿意和那些
Anyone who has a problem
有可能是变性人的人分享卫生间
sharing a bathroom with people who might be transgender
就得去用把他们和不介意这点的正常人
will have to use the special designated bathroom designed to
分隔开的特殊卫生间了
keep them away from the normal people who don't care.
你想干什么
Hey, where do you think you're going?
上厕所
To the bathroom.
不  不行
Oh, no, you don't!
你得用娘炮卫生间
You gotta use the cissy bathroom!
去吧  娘炮
Well go, cissy!
这里真棒
Wow, this is pretty nice.
*某个周一  感觉良好*
*Feelin' good on a monday*
*有了我自己的空间*
*Got my space all*
*我要的自由*
*Freedom I need*
*只有我自己*
*By myself*